stardewvalley.net 2019-12-25

# Stardew Valley - Privacy Policy

Effective Date: December 14, 2018

**CONCERNEDAPE PRIVACY POLICY**

ConcernedApe LLC, a Washington limited liability company (“ ** _ConcernedApe_** ”, “ ** _we_** ”, “ ** _us_** ” and their derivatives) makes this policy available to users of our websites, including [stardewvalley.net](http://stardewvalley.net/) and its subdomains (collectively, the “ ** _Websites_** ”), the Stardew Valley® videogame for PC, Playstation 4, PSVita, and Xbox (collectively, the “ ** _Game_** ”), and other online services we may provide (with the Websites and the Game, collectively, the “ ** _Services_** ”).

This policy describes our practices for collecting, using, transferring, disclosing, retaining and disposing of users’ personal data. Note that lowercase terms that are used but not defined in this policy ( _e.g._ , “personal data”, “controller”, “process”, “data subject”, etc.) have the meanings assigned in Article 4 of the European Union General Data Protection Regulation. To be clear, however, this policy applies to all users of the Services, no matter where they live.

This policy applies only to personal data we collect through the Services. It _does not_ apply to any information that we collect offline or you provide to or is collected by any third party.

Please read this policy carefully, so you can understand our policies and practices regarding your personal data. If you don’t agree with our policies and practices, don’t use our Services. By using our Services—including by using our Websites—you agree to this policy.

**Children**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from anyone under 13 years of age. Our Services are directed to people who are at least 13 years old. If you are under 13, do not submit any information about yourself to us. If you become aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, please contact us at concernedape@stardewvalley.net, so we may remove the information.

**Personal data we collect and how we collect it**

_Information from Third-Party Game Platforms_. We may automatically receive your personal data from the third-party platform ( _e.g._ , Steam, the Playstation Store, etc.) (each a “ ** _Third-Party Platform_** ”) through which you download and play the Game. The personal data we collect from a Third-Party Platform may include, by way of example, your name, the name of your account associated with the Third-Party Platform, and a list of your saved contacts with the Third-Party Platform ( _e.g._ , your “Steam Friends List”). Personal data collected by a Third-Party Platform is subject to such Third-Party Platform’s privacy policy ( _e.g._ , the [Steam Privacy Policy Agreement](https://store.steampowered.com/privacy_agreement/) and the [Playstation.com Privacy Policy](https://www.playstation.com/en-us/network/legal/privacy-policy/)). Information collected from Third-Party Platforms is used in accordance with the “How we use personal data” section below.

_Correspondence_. If you correspond with us electronically, we will retain records of our correspondence, including the contents of whatever was said, your email address, your name and any other information that you provide to us in such correspondence.

_Analytics_. If you browse our Websites, we may collect certain information about your use of our Websites. This information may include, without limitation, the number of page visits and duration, type of browser, etc. Some of this information, such as your IP address, may constitute personal data.

Data we collect about your use of the Websites may be collected through “cookies” and “web beacons”. Cookies are small files placed on the hard drive of your computer through your web browser that enable us to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Web beacons (also referred to as “clear gifs”, “pixel tags”, and “single-pixel gifs”) are small electronic files that enable us, for example, to count users who have visited our pages and for other related website statistics. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. Additionally, other online resources, such as [Privacy Badger from the Electronic Frontier Foundation](https://www.eff.org/privacybadger), are available that can help block certain automatic data collection technologies. Please note that, if you disable or refuse cookies or other automatic data collection technologies such as web beacons, some aspects of the Services may be inaccessible or not function properly.

**Where personal data is processed; transfer of personal data**

We’re based in the State of Washington in the United States of America. We may process and transfer your personal data in and to the United States of America and other countries, regardless of where you are. Note that the laws regulating the collection, use, and disposal of personal data vary from country to country, so applicable law in the country where your personal data may be processed may not be as comprehensive or strict as the laws of the country where you’re located.

**How we use personal data**

If you reach out to us directly, we will use your personal data to respond to you. When you play the Game, we may use personal data collected from the applicable Third-Party Platform in order to present the Game and its various features and functions to you. Where you’ve provided information to us for a specific purpose ( _e.g_., to help us troubleshoot an issue you’re having with the Services), we’ll use your information in furtherance of that purpose. We do not use automated decision-making in connection with the processing of your information.

We use automatic data collection technologies and the personal data collected through them to enable our Websites to remember you. We also use information gained through automatic data collection technologies to compile statistical information about use of our Websites, such as the pages users visit most often. We may use this information to improve our Services.

**Access to personal data by contractors and other third parties**

We may give certain independent contractors access to data we collect, including personal data. These independent contractors may assist us with tracking use of our Websites and the provision and improvement of the Services. Independent contractors that work for us are obligated to keep personal data confidential and use it only in accordance with our express instructions. We are not responsible for the conduct of any of our independent contractors.

_Google Analytics_

One of our independent contractors is Google Analytics. Google Analytics tracks and reports website traffic and monitors use of our Websites. Data collected may be shared with other Google services and used to target the ads of its own advertising network. It is our understanding that you can opt-out of Google Analytics tracking on our Websites by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on that prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit [the Google Privacy Terms web page](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

We also may disclose personal data:

  * to our subsidiaries and affiliates;
  * to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of ConcernedApe’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal data held by ConcernedApe pertaining to the users of our Services is among the assets transferred;
  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, such as responding to a government or regulatory request;
  * To enforce any contract we may have in effect with you such as our Terms of Services (available at [http://www.stardewvalley.net/terms]); and
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of us, our customers, or others.

**Legal bases for processing**

We rely on the following legal bases to process your personal data:

  * Your consent;
  * Compliance with applicable law;
  * Exercise of our legitimate interests in: 
    * Providing the Game and enabling our users to play the Game, including with one another;
    * Improving the Game;
    * Providing customer service;
    * Improving our Services and business;
    * Reviewing job applications; and
    * Addressing legal issues.
  * Fulfillment of our obligations to users of our Services; and
  * Endeavoring to protect users of our Services.

**Your data subject rights**

We will promptly act on the request of any user of the Services that we:

  * Confirm that we have their personal data;
  * Provide them with access to their personal data, including in portable format, that we may possess;
  * Correct, update or amend their personal data;
  * Delete and “forget” their personal data; or
  * Limit our processing of their personal data.

You may always withdraw any consent to process your personal data you have provided us and object to our use or disclosure of your personal data. Exercise of any of the rights set forth in this section may not apply retroactively from the date a given request is made and doesn’t affect our ability to continue processing personal data in accordance with this policy and applicable law. The rights described in this section are subject to certain limitations and exceptions under applicable law.

If you’d like to exercise any of your data subject rights concerning your personal data that we may possess, please reach out to us by email at concernedape@stardewvalley.net. When you reach out, please put “Data Subject Access Request” in the subject line of the e-mail, and briefly describe the right or rights you intend to exercise. We may use your personal data to confirm your identity before acting on your request.

You will always have the right to lodge a complaint about our privacy practices with the appropriate supervisory authority. We ask that you contact us first, so we can try to address any concerns that you have about our privacy practices directly.

**Data security and retention**

We retain personal data for only as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or provided, subject to certain exceptions as authorized by and where required under applicable law. We may pseudonymize, delete or take other measures to dispose of personal data. We may retain copies of personal data for additional time for business continuity purposes and for the purposes of creating backups.

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal data when you use the Services. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted. Such information is only accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems and that are required to keep the information confidential, subject to any additional requirements imposed by our contract with them and applicable law.

Also, please keep in mind that the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we have designed our Services with the protection of your personal data in mind, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal data transmitted through the Services. Any transmission of personal data is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Services.

**Changes to this policy**

If we make any changes to this policy, we will post the revised policy on this page and put a notice of the revision on the stardewvalley.net homepage. You are responsible for periodically visiting this page to check for any changes. The date the privacy policy was last revised is listed at the top of the policy.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions regarding this policy or our privacy practices, you may contact us at concernedape@stardewvalley.net.
